[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "Only with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 26, "question": "Why have you finally succumbed to me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CD", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "What changed your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "No, actually, I watched your show since day one and I -- you know, have been admiring it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Now they want me to ask, how many times have you been properly in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Is it to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "RBS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Who with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Well, the most recent and the most -- you know, the one I'd like to talk about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Who would the third be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Someone when I was much younger.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "You know that you have one relationship, I think, in your life that's kind of crazy and out of control a little bit that usually doesn't last very long but it takes you into the deep water, into the rough waves, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "The first time your heart really breaks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "You remember it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "And who broke whose heart?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "WP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "I was always the heart -- the first one, I got my heartbroken badly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "How did it change you emotionally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "I think, first of all, it opened me up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "But isn't the reality is, when you scale those dizzy height a lot of fun, though, a lot of it is, it can be a quite lonely existence, can it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Totally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Present company excepted, have you ever been in love with a man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike"]}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "Who?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "His name is Mike, and I've lived with him for about two years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "About convention, conventional relationships?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Well, about the societal approval that you got to have just by virtue of the fact that it was a heterosexual relationship.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Do you feel defensive more than you would normally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Not for me, I don't think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "And the three top ones are no longer in the race, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Yes, it's interesting to me that they're not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "What do you make of the GOP race generally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "You know, it's a sad lot of contenders.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["GOP"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Why do you feel there's still this fear of being open about sexuality in modern America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "Do you think mythology builds up about certainly celebrities?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "RB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "What's your overview now you've been in there a few months?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Well, I think that any new cable start-up takes about five to 10 years to really hit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "But when you two are together, these titans of American television, fire brands in many ways, trailblazers, what's the relationship like between you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "CD", "VBP", "RB", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "I feel like she's the smarter, prettier, older sister that you want to be like.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "She has a reach that is undeniable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Are you enjoying it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "A lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Let's turn to your family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "How are they all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "They're good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "And how about when you threaten to kill yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "RP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Do you like Twitter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Have I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "What were you expecting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "I was expecting mayhem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "'DONNELL: You think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "I've always thought that in different circumstances, you and I could be quite a hot couple.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "How much weight have you lost?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Sixteen pounds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Is that a stone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Yes, it's a stone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November 6th"]}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CD", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 410, "question": "In what space of time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "November 6th was the day I --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Two months, 16 pounds?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "'DONNELL: You know, working out and eating healthy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "You're very obedient then.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Have you learned to be obedient in a relationship?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "No, I am always sort of obedient in a relationship.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "I really do follow orders.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Starbucks"]}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "You met in a restaurant?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "We met at a Starbucks actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Million years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Have you seen her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "She's very attractive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Who proposed to who?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "TO", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "We had talked about it, you know, getting married, but I actually bought the ring and asked the question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "It was her exact word?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Well, it was freaking, but you get the point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Do any of them have any problems with you being gay that you picked up on or has it all worked out in a better way you could ever have imagined?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "I think it's worked out better because I'm a public figure and they didn't have to sort of tell their friends, or come out at school, everyone sort of just knew.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "It's humiliating and it was probably the most difficult thing that I ever went through in my adult life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "What was the moment for you when you realized it was irretrievable, that you were definitely going to have to split up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "When she said -- when she said that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "How do you get along with Kelly now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Really well.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kelly"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Did you invite her to your wedding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "I probably would invite her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["PTA"]}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "What do you remember about your mother?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "'DONNELL: She was the president of the PTA.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "What do you think she would have made of how you have grown up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "When you see people who have very close relationships with their mothers, do you feel like you've had this huge void in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "Always.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "So I would look in the mirror and I would be like, wow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "What must that have felt like for her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "IN", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "So she was aware.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Can you still cook it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "Brings back too many painful memories?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "That's sad, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "It is sad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "How did your father deal with it in reality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "You know, not very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Now that you've had four kids yourself, have you been able to look back on him in a more favorable light, given the enormity of what was suddenly thrust upon him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "In some ways, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "Have you reached that place?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "I have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Have you forgiven him, in your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "I have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 762, "question": "Are you surprised they invited him back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 763, "answer": "Shocked.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 782, "question": "You do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 783, "answer": "He's done me a lot of favors.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 808, "question": "He does?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 809, "answer": "Say something nice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kofi Annan"]}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "Is there a surprise guest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "I feel like Kofi Annan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 839, "question": "Yes, a confirmation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 840, "answer": "No, I wasn't given one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 855, "question": "How do you feel about being involved in one of the really appalling films ever made?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 856, "answer": "I'm happy I did it for two reasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 858, "question": "How do you go wrong with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 859, "answer": "Who is great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 882, "question": "Which is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 883, "answer": "Which is if I could let you relive --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 885, "question": "What would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 886, "answer": "It would be this interview, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 890, "question": "I have heard you ask that question a million times before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 891, "answer": "Admit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Rainbow Ranch"]}, "docId": "120117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 896, "question": "Can you remember a particular moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 897, "answer": "I remember on time we were driving home from Rainbow Ranch, which is where she would take my nana and herself to get dresses that were on sale.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]